<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Myrtle Beach's Best Real Estate Agent Training</title>
    <description>Scott Trembley, a top Real Estate Agent in Myrtle Beach, shares his own internal real estate agent training for free. His Real Estate Training, Tips and Advice will help you sell more homes in less time.</description>
    <link>https://realestatecareersmyrtlebeach.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://realestatecareersmyrtlebeach.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 10:01:41 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 10:01:41 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.2.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fellow Agents: It’s Time to Hold Yourself (and Your Team) Accountable</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/wy_HFFgGCE4?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you know, most agents don’t track the numbers in their business as closely as they should. If you fall into this category, don’t worry—you aren’t alone. But with that in mind, today I’d like to share a few of my team’s own methods for tracking our numbers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re thinking of taking control of your business and having a better life, in general, the first step we recommend is that you read Gino Wickman’s incredible book, “Traction.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=When we’re able to pinpoint our areas of weakness, we can use this knowledge to improve.%20https://realestatecareersmyrtlebeach.com/fellow-agents-its-time-to-hold-yourself-and-your-team-accountable.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“When we’re able to pinpoint our areas of weakness, we can use this knowledge to improve.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In addition to taking lessons from this book, our team has implemented a coaching scorecard.&lt;/strong&gt; We track appointments, sales, goals, and more for each and every agent. Agents are given points for their performance in each of these categories. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This gives us a clear idea of which of our agents are following the sales pipeline effectively, while simultaneously making us aware of the agents who could use some additional guidance. This is what makes tracking numbers so vital. When we’re able to pinpoint our areas of weakness, we can use this knowledge to improve. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give us a call or send us an email. We look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 11:27:09 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://realestatecareersmyrtlebeach.com/fellow-agents-its-time-to-hold-yourself-and-your-team-accountable.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://realestatecareersmyrtlebeach.com/fellow-agents-its-time-to-hold-yourself-and-your-team-accountable.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The 6 Steps to Buyer Loyalty</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/nFtiqyVgcKo?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In our fast-paced world of internet leads and online interaction with customers, it’s incredibly important to create buyer loyalty. Customers have more outlets than ever when it comes to business, &lt;strong&gt;so you need to have a way to set yourself apart from the competition and create value.&lt;/strong&gt; Today we’ll be looking at the six steps you should take to achieve buyer loyalty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=You must position yourself as a leader to your clients.%20https://realestatecareersmyrtlebeach.com/the-6-steps-to-buyer-loyalty.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“You must position yourself as a leader to your clients.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For your convenience, we’ve included timestamps for our topic today. Feel free to navigate to the section(s) you’re most interested in viewing:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;00:18— Introduction to our topic: The six steps to buyer loyalty&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;01:22— Commit to a buyer consultation before all showings&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;02:36— Get buy-in from clients that you will set up showings&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;03:18— Get them on your website&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;04:03— Take clients on three to five showings per outing&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;04:59— Set expectations for home showings&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;07:44— Set the future pace for the purchasing process&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;09:39— Recap of the six steps&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For these steps to work, you must position yourself as a leader to your clients by being confident, having a plan, and executing it. &lt;strong&gt;Hopefully this gave you a good idea of how to begin building loyalty with your clients and customers.&lt;/strong&gt; If you have any questions or need further information, feel free to reach out to me. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 08:58:37 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>https://realestatecareersmyrtlebeach.com/the-6-steps-to-buyer-loyalty.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://realestatecareersmyrtlebeach.com/the-6-steps-to-buyer-loyalty.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Scott Trembley's Journey Through Real Estate</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/JrZtDn1ZOK8?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 16:04:22 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>https://realestatecareersmyrtlebeach.com/scott-trembleys-journey-through-real-estate.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://realestatecareersmyrtlebeach.com/scott-trembleys-journey-through-real-estate.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What to Do When Your Buyer Wants to See 30 Homes</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/9zFps2t5PTo?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;present-before-paste present-before-paste&quot;&gt;What do you do when a client wants you to show them 30 homes? As an agent, there are several key tips you must remember and steps you must take in order to guide your clients through a timely, successful home purchase.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;present-before-paste&quot;&gt;First, remember that &lt;strong&gt;you must always be a leader.&lt;/strong&gt; In every relationship, someone has to lead and someone has to follow. So, when it comes to the real estate process, you must be a leader.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;present-before-paste&quot;&gt;Second, &lt;strong&gt;you have to have energy, enthusiasm, and confidence.&lt;/strong&gt; This ties in with the first point—people will respect and follow someone who has energy, enthusiasm, and confidence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;present-before-paste&quot;&gt;Third, &lt;strong&gt;always have a plan.&lt;/strong&gt; This applies whether you’re showing homes or doing a listing presentation. Just like people will respect someone with energy, enthusiasm, and confidence, they’ll also respect someone who has a plan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;present-before-paste&quot;&gt;Now that you know these main points, how do you apply them to the actual process?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;present-before-paste&quot;&gt;First, &lt;strong&gt;take a minute and slow down.&lt;/strong&gt; Sales agents sometimes get so excited on the front end of their client relationship that the back end becomes a mess. So, start asking your client why they want to see these 30 homes and what they are looking for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;present-before-paste&quot;&gt;To find this out, you need to &lt;strong&gt;identify their LPMAMA:&lt;/strong&gt; their preferred location, price, motivation, agent (make sure they’re not working with anyone else), mortgage (will they finance or pay cash?), and appointment time. Asking deep-level questions about all of these factors will help you understand what they’re looking for in a home while they still want to see 30 homes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;present-before-paste&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Their goal is to find the home they want and get into it as quickly as possible, and it’s your job to have an elimination and simplification strategy in place to make that happen.%20https://realestatecareersmyrtlebeach.com/what-to-do-when-your-buyer-wants-to-see-30-homes.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Their goal is to find the home they want and get into it as quickly as possible, and it’s your job to have an elimination and simplification strategy in place to make that happen.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;present-before-paste&quot;&gt;Now that you’ve narrowed the process down and you understand what your buyer is looking for, you need to &lt;strong&gt;summarize with them everything you’ve spoken about&lt;/strong&gt; to make sure you’re both on the same page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;present-before-paste&quot;&gt;After you’re done summarizing, you need to &lt;strong&gt;eliminate and simplify.&lt;/strong&gt; This is a very important step in this business. Take the summary of their 30 homes, discuss each one with them, and eliminate which ones won’t work. Your goal should be to simplify the list down to three to five homes by the time you meet with them. At the end of the process (or even during), they’ll thank you for taking this step and not wasting their time. Remember, their goal is to find the home they want and get into it as quickly as possible, and it’s your job to have an elimination and simplification strategy in place to make that happen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;present-before-paste&quot;&gt;I sometimes joke that agents who don’t take this step and actually end up showing 30 homes to their clients are like one-legged ducks walking in a circle. We’re in a resort market here, so even after their client buys their primary residence, they sometimes go back home feeling confused, so those agents have to then spend their time reeling that client back in. During that time, they may end up reaching out to another agent who can simplify the process for them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;present-before-paste&quot;&gt;Don’t be that agent. Be the one who goes through each of these steps thoroughly. After that, it’s go time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;present-before-paste&quot;&gt;If you have any other questions about this process or there’s anything else I can help you with, don’t hesitate to reach out to me. I’d love to speak with you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;present-before-paste&quot;&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://realestatecareersmyrtlebeach.com/what-to-do-when-your-buyer-wants-to-see-30-homes.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://realestatecareersmyrtlebeach.com/what-to-do-when-your-buyer-wants-to-see-30-homes.html</guid>
        
        <category>Buyer Prospects</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
